

hr@jiholee.me https://jiholee.me Anaheim, CA, 92801 (949) 233-8000



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jiho-lee-dev/

Authorized to work in the United States for any employer: STEM OPT-EAD (11/04/2021)

SUMMARY

Full-stack developer former designer; experience designing and developing front-end and back-end small and large projects. In a rapidly developing modern IT environment, always keep trying to learn and understand the flow of new technology. Regardless of platform, able to quickly hand-on and apply a variety of language, library, and framework.

EXPERIENCE

Jan 2019 - Present

Full Stack Developer • GIT (Hyundai KIA Motor Group)

Irvine California, US

Providing enterprise management service via vehicle diagnostic solution. DevOps inspection management system that integrates with Web Application, Mobile Android, iOS App, Desktop App, API WebService, SOAP, XML, JSON, on .NET framework.

Nov 2010 - Dec 2018

Full Stack Web Developer • Freelancer

Los Angeles California, US

B2B e-commerce marketplace with WooCommerce CMS WordPress, Magento, Shopify on AWS; others with LEMP, Node,js, jQuery, ASP.NET MVC, .NET Core

Nov 2008 - Sep 2010

Senior Web Developer • Wewelcom corp.

Anyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea

e-commerce solution classic ASP, C#.NET MSSQL, RESTful API, SOAP, XML

Aug 2005 - Nov 2008

Web Developer • SEJONG Telecom (FMR. Onse Telecom)

Seongnam, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea

GIS Web Map Roadmate, Navigation Software, Traffic Road data MRO. IIS, ASP, MSSQL, Oracle, COM+ Sockets, MFC, C#.NET, Window Form, Ajax Mar 2004 - Aug 2005

Assistant Engineer • Onse Telecom

GIS SI business, Signal simulator, UI Design, PDA app, Window Mobile 2003

Jan 2002 - Mar 2004

Designer & Developer • Seil I&C

Gwanak-gu, Seoul, South Korea

Designed and Developed branding franchise websites web application on LAMP

TECHNIQUES

Front-end

HTML5, CSS3, SaaS, Less Bootstrap, JavaScript, ES6, TypeScript, jQuery, Babel, Gulp SPA: Angular, React, Vue

Back-end

PHP, JSP, ASP, C#.NET, Laravel IIS, Apache, Tomcat, nginx, Node.js, MSSQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Redis NoSQL: MongoDB, MariaDB RESTful API, GraphQL

DevOps

Cloud: AWS, Azure, GCP, Heroku CI/CD: GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket JIRA, Confluence, Jenkins, Travis Docker, Vagrant, Kubernetes

CMSs

WordPress, Drupal, Joomla! XE3, WooCommerce, Magento Umbraco, GatsbyJS, Jekyll, Hugo

Extra...

Python, Django, Flask Java, Spring boot Ruby on Rails, Go React Native, Ionic, Flutter Agile Scrum Methodology

see more > https://jiholee.me

EDUCATION

Mar 2015 - Sep 2018

Pacific States University

Los Angeles California, US

Bachelor of Science, Computer Information Systems

Jan 2011 - Mar 2015

Santa Monica College

Santa Monica California, US

Associate of Science, Computer Programming